popgadget.net 2007-05-06

# Popgadget Privacy Policy

| 

Our Commitment to Privacy  
Your privacy is very important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and how we treat the information we collect when you visit our website or register/subscribe to receive information from us by email. Please read this statement carefully. 

The Information We Collect  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on or through the Popgadget website.

Personal Information  
To register for delivery by email of Popgadget updates and sponsored emails, we require your email address. At your option, additional personal information may be provided during registration or at other times, if you wish to participate in surveys or studies conducted by Popgadget. Popgadget does not collect any personal information that is not expressly provided by you. Popgadget will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except to professional third party service providers necessary to deliver the services (such as email delivery of issues) you expressly request.

Non-Personal Demographic Information  
In connection with registration to receive email updates or at other times, Popgadget may request optional demographic information such as age, income, occupation, geography and gender. Such information is used to compile anonymous, aggregate data not containing any personally identifiable information about you or other individuals. This aggregate, demographic data may be used to improve and customize our content to better serve our readers and subscribers, and may be shared with others, such as advertisers and potential partners or affiliates of PopLife Media.

Website Usage Information  
In addition to personal information and non-personal information as described above, PopLife Media or our partners or affiliates may collect non-personal, aggregate data about readers’ usage of our website. This aggregate data will contain no information personally identifying you or other individuals, and will only be used to better design our website and services.

Ownership of Information  
PopLife Media, LLC is the sole owner of all information collected on this website.

Registration/Subscription  
If you choose to register to receive popgadget updates by email, you will receive emails containing new stories added to our website. These emails may contain advertisements. In addition, occasionally, popgadget will deliver sponsored emails to subscribers, clearly identified as containing sponsored content from third parties.

Unsubscribe/Opt-Out  
If popgadget ever sends you information by email that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no future notices.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data sent by a web server and stored on a user’s browser. Like many websites, popgadget may use cookies to check subscriber status and preferences. PopLife Media will not use cookies to obtain data from a computer that is unrelated to our website and services. 

Third Party Cookies  
Some of our advertisers may use cookies on our website to track information such as the number of times an advertisement has been viewed (but not personal identifying information such as user names). PopLife Media may give third party advertisers permission to set cookies for advertising, but PopLife Media has no control over or access to such third party cookies.

Links  
Popgadget frequently provides links to third party websites; however, we are not responsible for the content that appears on those sites or the business or privacy practices of those sites. Please review the privacy policies contained in linked sites when you leave our website.

Traffic Reports  
Popgadget uses industry-standard tracking, which records Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP) information, referrer strings, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. Like most commercial websites, we use this information in the aggregate to analyze trends, administer the website, and gather broad demographic information. IP addresses and other data are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Our Commitment to Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Legal Disclaimer  
PopLife Media makes every effort to preserve user privacy; however, we may need to disclose information when required by law.

Changes to Privacy Policy  
From time to time, this privacy policy may be modified.

Contact  
Should you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please call us at 301-526-6370 or send us an e-mail at [info@popgadget.net](mailto:info@popgadget.net). 

Back to Top

| 

---|---|---
